

# Gabriel Muñoz Technology Manager

July 15, 1978

Seville, Spain +34 660227709

linkedin.com/in/fgabrielmunoz



fgabriel.munoz@tuta.io

## About me ———

More than 15 years of experience in software development, where I played all the roles: programmer, analyst, team leader and technology manager.

Extensive experience in different technologies, integration of complex systems, coexistence of legacy with modern software solutions and technological renovation processes.

# Skills —

**Team Management** 

Mobile

Java

Security

**PMP** 

Agile

CMMI

(\*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

#### Interests

I am particularly interested in those methodological approaches to increase the quality and predictability of software development processes, both classical methodologies (CMMI) and agile (Scrum, Kanban). Also in how to get both (classical and agile) work together. I am interested in international projects and/or related to University research and technological innovation.

#### **Education**

2012-2012	Executive Program in Project Management Preparatory to obtain the PMP certification	EOI - Ministry of Industry
2011-2012	Master's Degree in Business Administration Second best project of the promotion	EOI - Ministry of Industry
2000-2002	Computers Engineer's Degree Average grade: A	University of Granada
1996-1999	Computers Diploma of Higher Education Average grade: A	University of Cordoba

#### **Experience**

2018- Engineering Manager

Admiral Group

Direction of the technical team that gives cross service to all the Group's insurance companies in Europe in the following areas:

- Migration to the Amazon cloud (AWS)
- Security program (ISP)
- Design and evolution of technical architectures (software development and infraestructure)
- Development, deployment and operation of transversal systems shared between different countries
- · Methodology and processes

2003-2018 Technology Manager

Aytos Berger Levrault

I have had different stages in the last years:

- Since 2015, leading the technological renovation process, transforming legacy desktop solutions into innovative newgeneration products. I manage the technological strategy of Berger Levrault in Spain. I also participate as a technical reference in international projects from the Berger Levrault group (cloud strategy, sharing platform between countries, ...)
- In the period 2013-2015: leading the area of eGovernment, Architecture and Integrations. With a large team of development engineers we develop leading solutions in Document Management, BPM, Portals, eProcurement, Business Intelligence and mobile apps for Spanish Local Government.
- Previously, I assumed the job of Technical Product Manager in the Finance Area (Assets Management, Grants Management), leading development teams and projects.

2002-2003 Analyst-Developer

Coritel - Accenture

I participated mainly in two projects:

- Analysis and development of Corporate Intranet for Cepsa (a Spanish petroleum company).
- Development of Human Resources Supply System for *Correos* (the Spanish public mail company).

1999-2000 Developer

Aconsa - CajaSur

I was a developer in a project to build an ERP tailored to *CajaSur Renting*.

### Other information

Certifications

• OCA Java 8

- ITIL Foundation
- CMMI Associate
- Scrum Manager
- Cambridge First Certificate in English (B2)

#### Mobility

Driving license and international geographical mobility.